<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://ramyaln.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://ramyaln.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-06-27T20:09:24+00:00</updated><id>https://ramyaln.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">A short announcement</title><link href="https://ramyaln.github.io/blog/2025/short-announcement/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A short announcement"/><published>2025-06-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-06-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://ramyaln.github.io/blog/2025/short-announcement</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ramyaln.github.io/blog/2025/short-announcement/"><![CDATA[<p>I’ve always loved making sense of things — whether that’s parsing noisy RNA-seq data, figuring out why a metabolic readout doesn’t match a mouse’s behavior, or simply trying to understand what makes people tick.</p> <p>This space is where I unpack thoughts, questions, and discoveries — from research quirks to scientific rabbit holes I’ve wandered down. Some posts are reflective, some technical, and some just curious detours triggered by a dataset, a conversation, or a really weird paper.</p> <p><strong>A few things about me that don’t show up in a CV:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Even after four full rewatches of Attack on Titan, I still haven’t made peace with the ending.</li> <li>I love badminton, playing chess, and the emotional chaos of combat sports.</li> <li>And yes — I’m absolutely going to make it to an Ariana Grande concert one day. Manifesting…!</li> </ul> <p><strong>A quote that taught me to love science — in all its good and bad:</strong></p> <blockquote> <p><em>“…If a man never contradicts himself, the reason must be that he virtually never says anything at all.”</em><br/> <small>— <em>Erwin Schrödinger</em></small></p> </blockquote> <p>Thanks for reading — and for caring about ideas, science, and stories!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="personal"/><category term="announcement"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve always loved making sense of things — whether that’s parsing noisy RNA-seq data, figuring out why a metabolic readout doesn’t match a mouse’s behavior, or simply trying to understand what makes people tick.]]></summary></entry></feed>